[{"answer": "Our journey is not complete until all our children from the streets of Detroit, to the hills of Appalachia, to the quiet lanes of Newtown, know that they are cared for and cherished and always safe from harm.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "Day one, President Obama's second term, can he keep his promises to America on guns after another school shooting today?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "I think some of them are.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "My understanding is you have armed police specifically employed at the school and also civilian security, but they're not armed, is that correct?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Well, I think we have a different tone from President Obama than we've had in the past.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What was your reading of it?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, as we sit here tonight, I think it's limited what he can achieve.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "How successful can he be with the kind of quite ambitious plans that he laid out yesterday for what he wants to achieve?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "No, first of all, I don't think America's in bad shape at all.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Do you like the tenor of what you're hearing from him for his second term or is it fiddling while Rome burns?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you know, when we talk about debt, everybody likes to compare it to households.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "How can a country that's so riddled with debt actually not be in bad shape?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Perhaps that's true, but if you're one of the 8 percent who are unemployed and are actively pursuing employment, you feel it.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "What is the answer to that?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "I think it's a valid point to make.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Is that a valid point to make?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's a normal reaction, especially among us parents.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "If I had to sit and count, I can tell you almost all of them.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Did you know how many of the last 60 mass shootings have been in gun-free zones?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "But tell me this, I mean, do you go along then with this idea that you should arm almost everybody, at schools, at movie theaters?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "I mean, but where do you draw the line?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Let me answer -- let me answer your question.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "But why would your answer to bringing down that statistic which presumably we all want to do, why would the answer then be more guns?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "You are not going to bring down suicide numbers by having less guns.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "-- why would the way to bring down those numbers be to have even more guns?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "It was a shotgun, I think?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Yes, in this particular case, yes.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Do you need to have an assault weapon, an AR-15 military style rifle or do you believe that you were armed enough to do what you did, to defend yourself and your property and your family?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "You know, I mean, that's a tough question.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "How do we get through it?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "A member of the National Rifle Association, at the very beginning, said that we ought to include people who have been adjudicated as mentally unstable in the national -- in the list of people who can't get guns.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "And where can you see at least some kind of consensus?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Do you own a gun?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "A shotgun.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "What do you have?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Mark, do you have a gun?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Well, the government studies -- the Justice Department studies about the previous gun ban said it had no effect.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Do you believe that there's compelling evidence that an assault weapons ban, if it removed the loopholes that were there last time, would have no effect, zero effect?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I was not shot.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "And you were shot, too?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "One, I have no problem if you have guns in your home.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "What do you think of this debate?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "What many Americans don't realize is many countries around the world have brought in tough gun control, Japan, Australia, Britain and others.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Don't people watch \"Die Hard\" movies?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Piers, when the president says half the things he says, I'm not sure what he means by them.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "And that involves if they want to get married in America, getting married?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "It bothers me.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Doesn't that bother you?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Not climate, so to speak, but the weather day to day seems to be changing.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "But does that mean the climate is changing scientifically?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Well, that's a very good question.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Why am I taking a risk with my kids' and their kids' lives?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "1970S, we had global cooling.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "What do you say?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "What is your view, global warming?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "Seems to me the bulk of evidence supports climate change.", "docId": "130122pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "Frank?", "qSentId": 653}]